designersdigest.co 2011-10-07

# Privacy Policy | Copyright Policy

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by going to Contact page. 

At Designer’s Digest (http://designersdigest.co), the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by Designer’s Digest (http://designersdigest.co) and how it is used. 

## Log Files

Like many other Web sites, Designer’s Digest (http://designersdigest.co) makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. 

## Cookies and Web Beacons

Designer’s Digest (http://designersdigest.co) does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser. 

## DoubleClick DART Cookie

.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on Designer’s Digest (http://designersdigest.co).  
.:: Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to Designer’s Digest (http://designersdigest.co) and other sites on the Internet.  
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include Google Adsense.

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on Designer’s Digest (http://designersdigest.co) send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. 

Designer’s Digest (http://designersdigest.co) has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. 

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. Designer’s Digest’s (http://designersdigest.co) privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites. 

## Copyright Policy

All the resources like Vector Graphics, Stock Images, Photos, Graphics, etc. on this website are uploaded by users!

Some of the Resources are not allowed for commercial use, Make sure to read author’s terms of use before downloading it!

### What to do if I want you to remove certain copyrighted files from this blog?

Please note that we do not host any copyrighted content on this blog. The links that we post to the download files do not contain data that might be copyrighted in any way. However, we offer a service to remove the links from our blog if the copyright holder of the content requests so. These removal requests are only valid if:

  * You are, or your company is, the copyright holder of the content in question.
  * You provide the **exact** URLs to the files, **no** complete (sub)categories or search queries.
  * You provide the complete name(s) of the content in question.
  * You provide **full** contact information (including the name and phone number of the contact person), **not** a general anti-piracy mail address.

If your request complies with **all** of these rules use the contact page. Please keep the correspondence polite.  
We remove postings as soon as we can, usually within 24 hours. Keep in mind that we can only handle removal requests that comply with the rules mentioned above.

If you are not the owner of any files listed here, please stop complaining. If you do not like the content that you find here, you are free to leave.

Thanks  
Kevin S  
Designer’s Digest
